[Music]
I can't believe that I haven't figured
out by now every time I call you up all
you do is let me down
there was nothing bad as I could change
every time we try to be friends it
always ends insane
[Music]
something in me says
foreign
[Music]
something in me says whatever
and it brings me bad to you
my stupid heart don't know I tried to
let you go so many times
[Music]
tell me things
again and you can blame my stupid heart
thank you
[Music]
gonna tell me yes
lead back here
[Music]
I love it face your hands and legs let
me take care of it babe close your eyes
I'll sing your favorite song songs
[Music]
and I will give you everything
okay
I'm gonna kill you anyway
[Music]
I'll fix you with my love
thank you
everybody
[Music]
foreign
talk loud
[Music]
foreign
ladies
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
me me
oh
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
very much
if you know